ILGWU Oral History 5780 OH
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Benjamin Schlesinger (Box 593)
  - Benjamin Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 593, Folder 1)
- Benjamin Schlesinger (Box 594)
  - Benjamin Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 594, Folder 1)
- Benjamin Schlesinger (Box 595)
  - Benjamin Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 595, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 596)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 596, Folder 1)
    O.H. 12; Use copy
- Louis Stulberg (Box 597)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 597, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 598)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 598, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 599)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 599, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 600)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 600, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 601)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 601, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 602)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 602, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 603)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 603, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 604)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 604, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 605)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 605, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 606)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 606, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 607)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 607, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 608)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 608, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 609)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 609, Folder 1)
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 610)
  - Emil Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 610, Folder 1)
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 611)
  - Emil Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 611, Folder 1)
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 612)
  - Emil Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 612, Folder 1)
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 613)
  - Emil Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 613, Folder 1)
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 614)
  - Emil Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 614, Folder 1)
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 615)
  - Emil Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 615, Folder 1)
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 616)
  - Emil Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 616, Folder 1)
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 617)
  - Emil Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 617, Folder 1)
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 618)
  - Emil Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 618, Folder 1)
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 619)
  - Emil Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 619, Folder 1)
- Emil Schlesinger (Box 620)
  - Emil Schlesinger, 1974 (Box 620, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 621)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 621, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 622)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 622, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 623)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 623, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 624)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 624, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 625)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 625, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 626)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 626, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 627)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 627, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 628)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 628, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 629)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 629, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 630)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 630, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 631)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 631, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 632)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 632, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 633)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 633, Folder 1)
- Louis Stulberg (Box 634)
  - Louis Stulberg, 1976 (Box 634, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 635)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 635, Folder 1)
    O.H. 15; Use copy
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 636)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 636, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 637)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 637, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 638)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 638, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 639)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 639, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 640)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 640, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 641)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 641, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 642)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 642, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 643)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 643, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 644)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 644, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 645)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 645, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 646)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 646, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 647)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 647, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 648)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 648, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 649)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 649, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 650)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 650, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 651)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 651, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 652)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 652, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 653)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 653, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 654)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 654, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 655)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 655, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 656)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 656, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 657)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 657, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 658)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 658, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 659)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 659, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 660)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 660, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 661)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 661, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 662)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 662, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 663)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 663, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 664)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 664, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 665)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 665, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 666)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 666, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 667)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 667, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 670)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 670, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 671)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 671, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 672)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 672, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 673)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 673, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 674)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 674, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 675)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 675, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 676)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 676, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman (Box 677)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 677, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman OH 15 T10-T17 (Box 678)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 678, Folder 1)
    O.H. 15; Backup CD
- Charles Zimerman OH15 T1-T9 (Box 679)
  - Charles Zimmerman, 1975-1980 (Box 679, Folder 1)
- Antony Conticelli OH 7 (Box 680)
  - Antony Conticelli (Box 680, Folder 1)
    O.H. 7; Backup CD
- Samuel Sandhaus, William Ross OH10-OH11 (Box 681)
  - Samuel Sandhaus, William Ross (Box 681, Folder 1)
    O.H. 10, O.H. 11; Backup CD
- David Dubinsky, David Gingold OH2-OH3 - (Box 682)
  - David Dubinsky, David Gingold (Box 682, Folder 1)
    O.H. 2, O.H. 3; Backup CD
- Emil Schlesinger, David Zelinka OH5-OH6 - (Box 683)
  - Emil Schlesinger, David Zelinka (Box 683, Folder 1)
    O.H. 5, O.H. 6; Backup CD
- Charles Zimmerman OH15 T18-T25 (Box 684)
  - Charles Zimmerman (Box 684, Folder 1)
- Charles Zimmerman OH15 T26-T32 (Box 685)
  - Charles Zimmerman (Box 685, Folder 1)
- OH43 & 44 (Box 686)
  - Ida Weiss, Pauline Pepe (Box 686, Folder 1)
    O.H. 43, O.H. 44; Backup CD
- Israel Breslow OH24 t8-t15 (Box 687)
  - Israel Breslow (Box 687, Folder 1)
    O.H. 24; Backup CD
- Israel Breslow OH24 t16-t20 (Box 688)
  - Israel Breslow (Box 688, Folder 1)
- Isreal Breslow OH24 t1-t7 (Box 689)
  - Israel Breslow (Box 689, Folder 1)
- Rose Kaufman Fedorin, Nettie Harary Shrog OH38-40 (Box 690)
  - Rose Kaufman Fedorin, Nettie Harary Shrog (Box 690, Folder 1)
    O.H. 38; Backup CD
- Ruth R. Graeber & Eugene Coldstein, Morris Novik OH36-37 (Box 691)
  - Ruth R. Graeber & Eugene Coldstein, Morris Novik (Box 691, Folder 1)
    O.H. 36, O.H. 37; Backup CD
- Jack Faier, Ruth Rubenstein Graeber, Harry Schindler, Michael Bachrach OH31-35 (Box 692)
  - Jack Faier, Ruth Rubenstein Graeber, Harry Schindler, Michael Bachrach (Box 692, Folder 1)
    O.H. 31, O.H. 32, O.H. 33, O.H. 34, O.H. 35; Backup CD
- Nathaniel Minkoff, Fred Schmidt, Ida Weiss, Lula Read OH41-45 - (Box 693)
  - Nathaniel Minkoff, Fred Schmidt, Ida Weiss, Lula Read (Box 693, Folder 1)
    O.H. 41, O.H. 42, O.H. 43, O.H. 44; Backup CD
- Louis Stulberg OH12 t9-t11 (Box 694)
  - Louis Stulberg (Box 694, Folder 1)
    O.H. 12; Backup CD
- Louis Stulberg OH12 t1-t8 (Box 695)
  - Louis Stulberg (Box 695, Folder 1)
- Murray Gross OH16 t1-t9 (Box 696)
  - Murray Gross (Box 696, Folder 1)
    O.H. 16; Backup CD
- Bernard Shane OH13 t1-t7 (Box 697)
  - Bernard Shane (Box 697, Folder 1)
    O.H. 13; Backup CD
- Frank Gatti OH20 (Box 698)
  - Frank Gatti (Box 698, Folder 1)
    O.H. 20; Backup CD
- Shelley Appleton, Bertha Mandel Lanxner, Enrico Parenti, Samuel Weiss, Sara Borenstein, Josephine Stern OH14/17/18/21/22/25 (Box 699)
  - Shelley Appleton, Bertha Mandel Lanxner, Enrico Parenti, Samuel Weiss, Sara Borenstein, Josephine Stern (Box 699, Folder 1)
    O.H. 14, O.H. 17, O.H. 18, O.H. 21, O.H. 22, O.H.25; Backup CD
- John Denaro OH30 (Box 700)
  - John Denaro (Box 700, Folder 1)
    O.H. 30; Backup CD
- Clara Larsen, Joseph Roth, Mary Goff Shuster, Jennie Silverman OH26/27/28/29 (Box 701)
  - Clara Larsen (Box 701, Folder 1)
    O.H. 26, O.H. 27, O.H. 28, O.H. 29; Backup CD
- Abraham Plotkin OH19 t1-t8 (Box 702)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 702, Folder 1)
    O.H. 19; Backup CD
- Abraham Plotkin OH19 t7-t24 (Box 703)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 703, Folder 1)
- Abraham Plotkin OH19 t9-t16 (Box 704)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 704, Folder 1)
- Lazare Teper OH23 t1-t7 (Box 705)
  - Lazare Teper (Box 705, Folder 1)
    O.H. 23; Backup CD
- Abraham Plotkin OH19 t25-t32 (Box 706)
  - Abraham Plotkin (Box 706, Folder 1)
- OH23 t12a & 13b (Box 707)
  - Lazare Teper (Box 707, Folder 1)
- Lazare Teper OH23 t8a-t12&13 (Box 708)
  - Lazare Teper (Box 708, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 709)
  - Israel Breslow, 1982 (Box 709, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 710)
  - Israel Breslow, 1982 (Box 710, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 711)
  - Israel Breslow, 1982 (Box 711, Folder 1)
- Israel Breslow (Box 712)
  - Israel Breslow, 1982 (Box 712, Folder 1)
- Sarah Borenstein (Box 713)
  - Sarah Borenstein, 1982 (Box 713, Folder 1)
- Sarah Borenstein (Box 714)
  - Sarah Borenstein, 1982 (Box 714, Folder 1)
- Mary Goff Shuster (Box 715)
  - Mary Goff Shuster, 1982 (Box 715, Folder 1)
- Mary Goff Shuster (Box 716)
  - Mary Goff Shuster, 1982 (Box 716, Folder 1)
- Jenny Silverman (Box 717)
  - Jennie Silverman, 1982 (Box 717, Folder 1)
- Jenny Silverman (Box 718)
  - Jennie Silverman, 1982 (Box 718, Folder 1)
- Clara Larsen (Box 719)
  - Clara Larsen, 1982 (Box 719, Folder 1)
- Clara Larsen (Box 720)
  - Clara Larsen, 1982 (Box 720, Folder 1)
- Joseph Roth (Box 721)
  - Joseph Roth, 1983 (Box 721, Folder 1)
- Joseph Roth, 1983 (Box 722, Folder 1)
- John Denaro (Box 723)
  - John Denaro, 1983-1984 (Box 723, Folder 1)
- John Denaro (Box 724)
  - John Denaro, 1983-1984 (Box 724, Folder 1)
- John Denaro (Box 725)
  - John Denaro, 1983-1984 (Box 725, Folder 1)
- John Denaro (Box 726)
  - John Denaro, 1983-1984 (Box 726, Folder 1)
- John Denaro (Box 727)
  - John Denaro, 1983-1984 (Box 727, Folder 1)
- John Denaro (Box 728)
  - John Denaro, 1983-1984 (Box 728, Folder 1)
- John Denaro (Box 729)
  - John Denaro, 1983-1984 (Box 729, Folder 1)
- John Denaro (Box 730)
  - John Denaro, 1983-1984 (Box 730, Folder 1)
- Michael Bachrach (Box 731)
  - Michael Bachrach, 1983 (Box 731, Folder 1)
- Jack Faier (Box 732)
  - Jack Faier, 1983 (Box 732, Folder 1)
- Benjamin Follman (Box 733)
  - Benjamin Follman, 1983 (Box 733, Folder 1)
- Benjamin Follman (Box 734)
  - Benjamin Follman, 1983 (Box 734, Folder 1)
- Harry Schindler (Box 735)
  - Harry Schindler, 1983 (Box 735, Folder 1)
- Harry Schindler (Box 736)
  - Harry Schindler, 1983 (Box 736, Folder 1)
- Harry Schindler (Box 737)
  - Harry Schindler, 1983 (Box 737, Folder 1)
- Graeber (Box 738)
  - Ruth Rubenstein Graeber, 1983 (Box 738, Folder 1)
- Graeber (Box 739)
  - Ruth Rubenstein Graeber, 1983 (Box 739, Folder 1)
- Graeber (Box 740)
  - Ruth Rubenstein Graeber, 1983 (Box 740, Folder 1)
- Graeber (Box 741)
  - Ruth Rubenstein Graeber, 1983 (Box 741, Folder 1)
- Morris Novik (Box 742)
  - Morris Novik, 1984-1985 (Box 742, Folder 1)
- Morris Novik (Box 743)
  - Morris Novik, 1984-1985 (Box 743, Folder 1)
- Morris Novik (Box 744)
  - Morris Novik, 1984-1985 (Box 744, Folder 1)
- Morris Novik (Box 745)
  - Morris Novik, 1984-1985 (Box 745, Folder 1)
- Morris Novik (Box 746)
  - Morris Novik, 1984-1985 (Box 746, Folder 1)
- Morris Novik (Box 747)
  - Morris Novik, 1984-1985 (Box 747, Folder 1)
- Morris Novik (Box 748)
  - Morris Novik, 1984-1985 (Box 748, Folder 1)
- Graeber (Box 749)
  - Ruth Rubenstein Graeber, Eugene Goldstein, and Nettie Harary Shrog, 1985 (Box 749, Folder 1)
- Graeber (Box 750)
  - Ruth Rubenstein Graeber, Eugene Goldstein, and Nettie Harary Shrog, 1985 (Box 750, Folder 1)
- Graeber (Box 751)
  - Ruth Rubenstein Graeber, Eugene Goldstein, and Nettie Harary Shrog, 1985 (Box 751, Folder 1)
- Shrog (Box 752)
  - Nettie Harary Shrog, 1985 (Box 752, Folder 1)
- Shrog (Box 753)
  - Nettie Harary Shrog, 1985 (Box 753, Folder 1)
- Shrog (Box 754)
  - Nettie Harary Shrog, 1985 (Box 754, Folder 1)
- Shrog (Box 755)
  - Nettie Harary Shrog, 1985 (Box 755, Folder 1)
- Shrog (Box 756)
  - Nettie Harary Shrog, 1985 (Box 756, Folder 1)
- Shrog (Box 757)
  - Nettie Harary Shrog, 1985 (Box 757, Folder 1)
- Shrog (Box 758)
  - Nettie Harary Shrog, 1985 (Box 758, Folder 1)
- Rosenberg (Box 759)
  - Rose Newmark Rosenberg, 1985 (Box 759, Folder 1)
- Fedorin (Box 760)
  - Rose Kaufman Fedorin, 1985 (Box 760, Folder 1)
- Fedorin (Box 761)
  - Rose Kaufman Fedorin, 1985 (Box 761, Folder 1)
- Fedorin (Box 762)
  - Rose Kaufman Fedorin, 1985 (Box 762, Folder 1)
- Schmidt (Box 763)
  - Fred Schmidt, 1985 (Box 763, Folder 1)
- Nathaniel Minkoff (Box 764)
  - Nathaniel Minkoff, 1975 (Box 764, Folder 1)
- Ida Weiss (Box 765)
  - Ida Weiss, 1986 (Box 765, Folder 1)
- Ida Weiss (Box 766)
  - Ida Weiss, 1986 (Box 766, Folder 1)
- Ida Weiss (Box 767)
  - Ida Weiss, 1986 (Box 767, Folder 1)
- Ida Weiss (Box 768)
  - Ida Weiss, 1986 (Box 768, Folder 1)
- Pauline Pepe (Box 769)
  - Pauline Pepe, 1986 (Box 769, Folder 1)
- Lula Read (Box 770)
  - Lula Read (Box 770, Folder 1)
- Lula Read (Box 771)
  - Lula Read (Box 771, Folder 1)
- Fred Schmidt (Box 772)
- Ruth Rubenstein Graeber + Duegen Goldstein (Box 773)
- Nettie Harary Shrog (Box 774)
- Rose Newmark Rosenberg (Box 775)
- Triangle Fire Oral Histories - Maizler, Hochfield, Pepe (Box 776)
- Joseph Roth (Box 777)
- Ida Weiss - (Box 778)
- Oral History #35.3 (Box 779)
- Oral History #35.2B (Box 780)
- Oral History #35.2A (Box 781)
- Ruth Rubinstein Graeber, Pins + Needles (Box 782)
- Oral History #37.1 (Box 783)
- Oral History #37.2A (Box 784)
- Oral Hisotry #38.1B (Box 785)
- Oral History #38.2A (Box 786)
- Oral History #38.2B (Box 787)
- Oral Hisotory #38.3 (Box 788)
- Oral History #38.4B (Box 789)
- Oral History #38.4A (Box 790)
- Oral History #40.1A (Box 791)
- Oral Hisotry #40.1B (Box 792)
- Oral History #40.2 (Box 793)
- Triangle Fire Survivor Oral Hisotires - UNITE HERE -- Dora Maizler; Max Hochfield; Pauline Pepe (Box 794)
- Triangle Fire Survivor Oral histories -- Dora Maizler; Max Hochfield; Pauline Pepe (Box 795)
- Triangle Fire - 3 Oral Histories -- Max Hochfield; Dora Maizur; Pauline Pepe (Box 796)
- Triangle Fire Oral Histories WAV files (Box 797)
- O.H. 2 - David Dubinsky - 6/25/1974 (Box 798, Folder 1)
- O.H. 2 - David Dubinsky - 7/10/1974 (Box 799, Folder 1)
- O.H. 2 - David Dubinsky - 7/24/1974 (Box 800, Folder 1)
- O.H. 2 - David Dubinsky - 8/21/1974 (Box 801, Folder 1)
- O.H. 3 - David Gingold by Gus Tyler - 2/28/1974 (Box 802, Folder 1)
- O.H. 3 - David Gingold by Gus Tyler - 4/3/1974 & 7/25/1974 (Box 803, Folder 1)
- O.H. 3 - David Gingold by Gus Tyler - 7/25/1974 (Box 804, Folder 1)
- O.H. 3 - David Gingold by Gus Tyler - 8/22/1974 (Box 805, Folder 1)
- O.H. 3 - David Gingold by Gus Tyler - 8/28/1974 (Box 806, Folder 1)
- O.H. 3 - David Gingold by Gus Tyler - 12/3/1974 (Box 807, Folder 1)
- Ida Weiss -- OH 43 (4/30/1986) (Box 808)
- Audio digitized from the collection. (Box 809)